https://www.hairutopia.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

CHILDREN'S HAIR GOODS & MORE
CHRISTMAS, HALLOWEEN, EASTER, VALENTINES DAY, AND OTHER HOLIDAY
HEADBAND HEADWRAPS
CLAW CLIPSBestsellers...1 - Scunci 8 CT Black Elastics2 - ta-22, gross for per order3 - Name Brand High Count Elastics Mix...4 - Ponytialer Elastic Diverse Bundle...5 - Wet N Wild Pack Emery Boards/...6 - Goody, Scunci, Conair, Vidal...7 - 18138448 - Diverse Hair Accessories - GOODY,...9 - Goody Luxe Black Bead Variety...10 - Thin Smooth Satin Headband - Black... Specials ... New Products ... Featured Products ...
All Products ...Home
New Products
Featured
All Products
Specials
Best Sellers
Search
Information
CHILDREN'S HAIR GOODS & MORE
CHRISTMAS, HALLOWEEN, EASTER, VALENTINES DAY, AND OTHER HOLIDAY
COSMETICS & BEAUTY
DISPLAYS AND MIXED LOTS
ELASTICS, PONYTAILERS AND SCRUNCHIES
Ethnic Hair Care
FEATHER HAIR ACCESSORIES & JEWELS
GENERAL MERCHANDISE
HAIR BEAUTY CARE: BRUSH, COMB, GIFT SETS
HAIR SCISSORS
Reward Points
No points earned yet on current order.Log in to see how many reward points you have already earned
Sponsors
Home
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Hairutopia is committed to providing its customers with complete privacy. You can shop for our wholesale hair and fashion accessories with confidence.
By visiting Hairutopia , you are accepting the practices described in this privacy statement. Our site uses a shopping cart ordering system that collects personal information (name, address, telephone number, etc.) and financial information (account or credit card number) from the customer. This contact information is used to send orders and information about our company to you and to get in touch with our customers when necessary.
Financial information is used solely for the purpose of billing customers for products ordered. We do not keep credit card information on file for future use. We thank our repeat customers for their patience in resubmitting their credit card details with subsequent orders.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect against the unauthorized access and misuse of customer information. Our secure ordering system uses SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption technology to keep your credit card transactions and other information safe. We do not employ the use of cookies for storing the contents of your shopping cart between visits. We guarantee the safety of shopping online with Hair Utopia. However, if you are not comfortable providing personal and financial information over the Internet, please call us at 360-866-8840 to complete your order.
Effective Date & Amendments
This policy is effective beginning October 26, 2003. Amendments to this policy will be posted at this URL and will be effective when posted.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with Hairutopia, please contact:
Copyright © 2020 Treasure Hunt Products.
Powered by Zen Cart
Site Map
Privacy Notice
Conditions
